mainrobots.com 2019-04-05

# Privacy Policy | Mainrobots Limited

This Privacy Policy is intended to describe how your personal information is processed and used. Please note that by visiting and using mainrobots.com, you are accepting the practices described.

Every computer connected to the internet is provided with a domain name and an ip-address. When a visitor requests a web page from the site, our server automatically identify and log the HTTP request that is made.

This information reveals nothing personal about you. In fact, the only information that we automatically gather and log is as follows: the ip-address of the site that may have referred you; your ip-address; the web page that you may have linked to us from, if any; the product identifier for version and make of browser (e.g. Google Chrome); the operating system platform that you may be running (e.g. Macintosh or Windows); search words or terms that are passed from a search engine (e.g. Google).

Mainrobots has found it advantageous to examine visitor traffic so that we can ensure maximum compatibility for the various browsers and operating systems that visit our site. By analysing visitation patterns, referring URLs and search engine terms, we can strategically enhance our exposure across the Internet.

When we provide services, we want to make them easy, useful and reliable. Where services are delivered on the internet, this sometimes involves placing small amounts of information on your device, for example, your computer or mobile phone. These include small files known as cookies. They cannot be used to identify you personally.

Mainrobots Company uses all reasonable precautions to keep the information disclosed to us secure. In order to protect the privacy of our clients, our program doesn't require them to provide their ID, photos or any other documents that may cause damage or distress.

The information gathered during the use of this service is used solely to simplify the user account administration. Client information is confidential and can't be disclosed to third parties.

Mainrobots Company is not responsible for personal information leakage if the client accidentally or intentionally has provided access to his/her account to third parties. Furthermore, we are not responsible for any breach of security or for any actions of any third parties that receive the information. In order to avoid personal information disclosure, we recommend using antivirus program, firewall, and not to open emails sent from unknown senders and not to follow links in these emails.

In order to protect your personal information, we warn our clients that it never, under any pretext, ask for login, password or access to a personal email box of the client. If you have received such a letter, don't respond to it and notify our [support](https://mainrobots.com/?a=support). 

### Mainrobots Financial Statistics

We are dedicated to providing our customers with outstanding service and investment plans that are second to none. We are completely transparent to our current and future customers, so we update and demonstrate the results of our investment activity in real time.

4081666.51USD

Total invested

1553424.95USD

Total withdrawal

Copyright © 2018 - 2019 Mainrobots Limited. All rights reserved.
